{
    "subject": "Jessica_Buchanan",
    "predicate": "hasChild",
    "object": "Nash_Brennan",
    "human_readable": "Jessica Buchanan has a child named Nash Brennan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9713308215141296,
            "question": "Is Nash Brennan related to Jessica Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9676221609115601,
            "question": "Who has a child named Nash Brennan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9239164590835571,
            "question": "Name Jessica Buchanan's child."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8587185144424438,
            "question": "What is the name of Jessica Buchanan's child?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8446398377418518,
            "question": "What is the full name of Jessica Buchanan's child?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8187793493270874,
            "question": "Who is Nash Brennan's parent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8113287091255188,
            "question": "Does Jessica Buchanan have children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7810143232345581,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Jessica Buchanan and Nash Brennan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4637759029865265,
            "question": "Is Jessica Buchanan a mother?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4320846498012543,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Nash Brennan's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jessica Buchanan has a child named Nash Brennan.",
            "html": "yago_30420_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jessica Buchanan a mother?",
            "html": "yago_30420_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Jessica Buchanan and Nash Brennan?",
            "html": "yago_30420_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Jessica Buchanan have children?",
            "html": "yago_30420_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30420_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe context information provides details about the characters and storylines of the American soap opera One Life to Live. It mentions that Nash Brennan is the son of Jessica Buchanan, but it does not indicate that Jessica has a child named Nash Brennan. In fact, the text states that Nash and Jessica are fictional characters who have a daughter named Bree (also known as Brennan \"Bree\" Buchanan), and not a child-named Nash Brennan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not support the statement that Jessica Buchanan has a child named Nash Brennan. Instead, the documents indicate that Bree Brennan is their daughter, born after Jessica and Nash's relationship and marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}